<odoo>
  <data>

    <template id="new_offer_letter_report_document">
    <div class="header">
				<div class="row">
					<div class="col-xs-3">
      <img src="https://imgur.com/gLIZY9S.jpg" style="max-height: 150px;" />

					</div>
					<!--<div class="col-xs-offset-2 text-right">
						<img src='/construction_rewrite/static/img/logobh.png' style="max-height: 45px;"/>
					</div>-->



				</div>
				<hr/>
			</div>
   <t t-foreach="docs" t-as="o">
               <!-- <t t-call="report.internal_layout">-->

            <div class="page" style="max-width: 660px; margin: auto;">

        <style>

					body {
					  line-height: 180%;
						font-size: 18px;
						font-family: 'EB Garamond';
					}

					page {
						margin-bottom: -30px;
					}

					p {
					  text-align: justify;
						margin: 0;
					}

          .abc {
  				margin-left: 40px;
    			list-style-type: lower-alpha;
				 }

					li {
					  text-align: justify;
						padding-top: 2%;
						padding-bottom: 20px;
					}
				</style>

            <p><t t-esc="datetime.datetime.now().strftime('%B %d, %Y')" /></p>
				<br />

                <span t-field="o.partner_id"/>,<br/>
                <span t-field="o.partner_id.street"/>,<span t-field="o.partner_id.street2"/>,<br/>
                <span t-field="o.partner_id.city"/>,<span t-field="o.partner_id.state_id.name"/>,<br/>
                <span t-field="o.partner_id.country_id.name"/> <br/>

        <p align="justify">
            Dear Sir/Madam,
        </p>

        <h4 style="text-align: center;"><strong><u>PROVISIONAL LETTER OF ALLOCATION OF A <span t-esc="o.build_type" /> AT BRAINS &amp; HAMMERS ESTATE, <span t-esc="o.name.name" />, ABUJA</u></strong></h4>

        <p>Further to your application, we are pleased to inform you that House No <strong><span t-esc="o.plot_no.plot_no" /> </strong>at Brains and Hammers Estate, has been allocated to you.</p>

        <p>The purchase price of the property: - &#8358;<strong><span t-esc="'{0:,}'.format(int(o.offer_price))"/></strong>  Naira only. exclusive of taxes and VAT.</p>

        <p>Kindly quote this unique reference number <strong><span t-esc="o.so_no" /></strong> in every transaction pertaining this offer on house <t t-esc="o.plot_no.plot_no" />.</p>

        <p><strong>TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF OFFER</strong></p>

          <ol style="padding-left: 70px;">

            <t t-if="o.payment_breakdown">

  						<li>
  							Accepting and returning this offer letter within one week from the offer date with the evidence of payment of an initial deposit of <strong>N<span t-esc="'{0:,}'.format(int(o.payment_breakdown[0].amount_to_pay))"/></strong> into the accounts of Brains and Hammers Limited.
                Please note that you must quote your reference number on your deposit slip for all payments to be made (<strong><span t-esc="o.so_no" /></strong>).
  						</li>

  						<t t-foreach="o.payment_breakdown[1:-1]" t-as="payment">
  							<li>
  							Payment of the sum of &#8358;<strong><span t-esc="'{0:,}'.format(int(payment.amount_to_pay))"/></strong> being additional <span t-esc="float(payment.amount_to_pay/o.offer_price * 100)" />% of the purchase price <span t-esc="int(payment.interval.split(' ')[0])"/> days (<span t-esc="payment.interval.split(' ')[0]"/>) from the date of the payment stated under clause <span t-esc="payment_index + 1" /> of this provisional offer.
  							</li>
  						</t>
			</t>


  					<t t-if="not o.payment_breakdown">
  						<li>
  						Accepting and returning this offer letter within one week from the offer date with the evidence of payment of a total deposit of &#8358;<strong><span t-esc="'{0:,}'.format(int(o.offer_price))"/></strong> into the accounts of brains and hammers limited.
  						</li>
  					</t>

           <!-- <t t-set="result" t-value="0" />
             <t t-if="o.payment_invoice.invoice_line_ids.invoice_line_tax_ids">

            <li>Value Added tax (V.A.T) being <t t-foreach="o.payment_invoice.invoice_line_ids" t-as="taxe">

                                                 <span t-esc="taxe.invoice_line_tax_ids[0].amount"/>%

             of the purchase price &#8358;<span t-esc="'{0:,}'.format(int(taxe.invoice_line_tax_ids[0].amount*o.payment_invoice.amount_total /100))"/></t> </li>
            </t>
            <t t-if="not o.payment_invoice.invoice_line_ids.invoice_line_tax_ids">

            <li>Value Added tax (V.A.T) being <span t-esc="result"/>%

             of the purchase price &#8358;<span t-esc="'{0:,}'.format(int(o.payment_invoice.amount_total))"/></li>
            </t> -->

             <li>Value Added Tax (V.A.T) being <t t-set="taxs" t-value="5"/><span t-esc="taxs"/>% of the purchase price &#8358;<span t-esc="'{0:,}'.format(int(taxs*o.payment_invoice.amount_total /100))"/> </li>

             <li>Total amount payable by Allottee &#8358;<span t-esc="'{0:,}'.format(o.payment_invoice.amount_total + taxs*o.payment_invoice.amount_total /100)"/></li>

            <li>Notwithstanding the provisions of Clauses 1, 2 and 3, of this agreement regulating the terms of payment for the housing unit provisionally allocated to the Allotee both the Vendor and Allotee agree that the commencement date which is the date for the commencement of construction works of the Allotee’s housing unit shall be the date as communicated by the Vendor to the allotee and where there is a variation of such commencement date then it shall be any further date as  communicated by the Vendor to the Allotee.</li>

            <li>Notwithstanding the provisions of Clauses 1, 2 and 3, of this agreement regulating the terms of payment for the housing unit provisionally allocated to the Allotee both the Vendor and Allotee agree that the duration construction time of this agreement shall be such period as communicated by the Vendor to the Allotee and where there is a variation of the duration construction time any further date as communicated by the Vendor to the Allotee</li>

            <li>Notwithstanding the provisions of Clauses 1, 2 and 3, of this agreement regulating the terms of payment for the housing unit provisionally allocated to the Allotee both the Vendor and Allotee agree that the completion date shall the date as communicated by the Vendor to the Allotee and where there is a variation and or extension of the completion time as communicated by the Vendor any further date as communicated by the Vendor to the Allotee.</li>

            <li>Where any Allotee provisionally allocated a housing unit under the Nine(9) Months payment plan has refused, neglected or failed to make any of its stage payment(s) as provided for under its Nine(9) Months payment plan such an allotee shall be migrated to the Twenty Four(24) Months payment plan by the Vendor in its sole discretion and the Vendor shall inform the Allotee of its migration to the Twenty Four(24) Months payment plan provided that and it is hereby agreed that where the Vendor is unable to accommodate any such Allotee under the Twenty Four Months(24) Months payment plan it shall refund the Allotee its deposit( less ten percent of the full purchase price which shall be deducted as administrative fees) where it has when a buyer has been found by the Vendor and the said buyer has made full payment for the housing unit.</li>

            <li>Where an Allotee who is provisionally allocated a housing unit under the Nine(9) Months payment plan has refused, neglected or failed to make any of its stage payment(s) as provided for under its Nine(9) Months payment plan such an allotee shall be migrated to the Twenty Four(24) Months payment plan by the Vendor in its sole discretion and the Vendor shall inform the Allotee of its migration to the Twenty Four(24) Months payment plan and the Vendor shall provide the Allotee with a housing unit of the same house type and specification as previously allocated to the Allotee.</li>

            <li>The Vendor and Allotee hereby agree that the migration from the Nine (9) Months payment plan to the Twenty Four(24) Months payment plan shall attract a variation of the cost price of the housing unit. The new purchase price of the housing unit shall be communicated by the Vendor to the Alloteeand the Allotee shall be required to pay for the housing unit at the new purchase price.</li>

            <li>Notwithstanding any provisions of this agreement the Nine (9) Months payment plan for the Vendor’s house type product(s) shall refer to the period only of the stages of payment to be adopted by the Allotee in making payment for their allotted housing unit as agreed with the Vendor and shall not refer to the commencement date for the construction of the Allotee’s housing unit or the duration of the construction of their housing unit and or completion date for the construction of their housing unit.</li>

            <li>Notwithstanding any provisions of this agreement the Twenty Four (24) months payment plan for the Vendor’s house type product(s) shall refer to the stages of payment to be adopted by the Allotee in making payment for their allotted housing unit as agreed with the Vendor and shall not refer to the commencement date for the construction of the Allotee’s housing unit or the duration of the construction of their housing unit and or completion date for the construction of their housing unit </li>

            <li>Each Allotee shall in making any of the stage payment to the Vendor’s account or any payment with respect to any housing unit allotted to them include in their deposit slips their name(s) and if a corporate entity their corporate name along with the provisional house number, reference number and the specific housing estate of the housing unit they are paying for.</li>

            <li>This allocation letter is provisional and upon the Allotee fulfilling the terms and conditions contained herein the Allotee shall be issued by the Vendor with a final letter of allocation and thereafter the Deed of sublease. The Provisional letter of allocation is not title to the semi-finished housing unit and cannot be used by any Allotee to sell, assign, transfer any interest to a third party in respect of any housing unit(s).</li>

            <li>Each Allotee shall where they have given instructions to any agent or representative to make any of the stage payments on their behalf shall ensure compliance by any such agent or representative with clause 10 of this agreement.</li>

            <li>Where any Allotee has made any stage payment in furtherance to the terms of this provisional sales agreement such an Allotee shall not in any circumstances whatsoever be entitled to a refund of such deposits made in pursuance to this agreement save for where in pursuant to the terms of this agreement the provisional allocation is terminated by the vendor for failure by the Allotee to make a stage payment( under the Nine (9) Months payment plan and or Twenty Four(24) payment plan) as and when due under this agreement provided as always that the Vendor shall make refunds to the Allotee of the deposit made for the housing unit (less a Ten percent (10%) of the full purchase price deduction from the of the full purchase) by the Vendor as administrative fees notwithstanding that the Allotee has not completed payment for the housing unit and upon the purchase and full payment for the said allocation by a third party.</li>

            <li>By the terms of this provisional letter of allocation the Vendor holds itself out as possessing the requisite technical and professional skill and competence to execute the terms of this contract while the Allotee holds itself out as having the immediate source of funds to pay for the execution of the terms of this agreement as such no Allotee shall determine this agreement on the basis that it does not have a sufficiency of funds to pay or continue to pay for the commencement, continuation and completion of the execution of the terms of this agreement or make the stage payments as agreed by the Vendor and the Allotee under this Agreement.</li>

            <li>The Vendor shall be under obligation to deliver on the terms and conditions of this agreement to wit the delivery of the housing unit(s) due for which payment has been made by the Allotee under the terms of this agreement and shall not be under any obligation whatsoever for the refund of monies paid for the commencement, continuance and completion of the housing unit due under the terms of this agreement (save for as provided for in this agreement) and both the Vendor and the Allotee further agree that the Vendor’s obligation to the Allotee under the terms of this agreement shall only be with respect to the delivery of any such housing unit(s) as agreed under the terms of this agreement and that the Allotee shall not be entitled to any monetary refund at any stage of the execution of works with respect to the housing unit(s) except as under the circumstances stated in this agreement.</li>


            <li>The cost of perfection of the title shall be borne by the Allotee.</li>

            <li>Documentation and Legal Fee: The Allotee shall pay 1% of the value of the purchased property as documentation and Legal fees. Payment shall be by bankers’ cheque or draft in the name of <b>Abubakar Sheidu &amp; co.</b> which shall be made at the payment of the third instalment.</li>

            <li>
                  The Allotee shall be given possession of the property upon full payment of the aforementioned purchase price as well as the legal fees, service charges, infrastructure leasing charges, generator meter, AEDC meter, water meter, water pumps at the housing units and automatic change over switch, waste bin, as well as other impositions herein-contained and all allocations are provisional until all payments have been received by the Vendor. The Facility Management Office within the Estate will communicate the prices to the Allotee(s).</li>


            <li>The Vendor shall directly or through its nominated agents undertake the provision of the Facility Management Services within the Estate including but not limited to the following; provision of security personnel, provision of external cleaners, generator servicing, external electrical equipment servicing, gardening, cleaning and horticulture works, fumigation, plumbing works, regular servicing of fire-fighting equipment, management and disposal of waste disposal units, keeping of the common grounds, pavements, street lightings, roads and other facilities and the cost of all such services shall be subject to periodic review from time to time as determined by the Vendor. </li>

            <li>The Capital Charge is now to be referred to as the Infrastructural Leasing Charge and any prior reference to the term capital charge shall mean infrastructure leasing charge with regard to any prior documentation issued by the Vendor to any Allotee.</li>

            <li>The cost of leasing and maintaining ( that is maintenance based on wear and tear and not as occasioned by negligence of any residence of the Estate) by the Allotees of infrastructural facilities provided and owned by the Vendor within the Estate such as transformers, ring main units, the perimeter fence, entry gates, the boreholes, water pumping machines (both surface and submersible) road reconstruction, reconstruction of drainages, culverts, purchase and replacement of damaged or destroyed street lights, replacement of armoured cables, replacement of the electric fence, replacement of water reservoir tank(s)purchase of new feeder pillars, replacement of low voltage panels, replacement of high voltage panels, reconstruction of security house, replacement of Abuja Electrical Distribution Company (AEDC) skipper or maximum demand meters, water treatment plant(s), central storage bins, diesel storage tank(s), lightening protection system(s), synchronizing panels, street signage(s) and closed circuit security systems (CCTV) shall be borne by all Allotees by the payment of an infrastructure leasing charge annually in the amount as provided for in the final letter of allocation.</li>

            <li>The service charge shall be paid in advance by each Allotee and the amount shall be as provided for in the final allocation letter to be issued by the Vendor to each Allotee.</li>

            <li>The service charge shall be subject to periodic review from time to time as determined by the Vendor. </li>

            <li>The Infrastructure leasing charge shall be paid in advance by each Allotee and the amount shall be as provided for in the final allocation letter to be issued by the Vendor to each Allotee.</li>

            <li>The Infrastructure leasing charge shall be subject to periodic review from time to time as determined by the Vendor. </li>

            <li>The Service charge and the Infrastructure leasing charge must be paid along with the purchase price of the allotted unit and every year thereafter. </li>

            <li>The Service charge and the Infrastructure leasing charge shall be paid at the same time by the Allotee to the account designated by the Vendor or to the Vendor’s authorised representative and each Allottee must state in their payment slips the number of their housing unit and the specific estate they have been allotted a housing unit. </li>

            <li>Failure to effect payment of the Service charge and the Infrastructure leasing charge shall result in the withdrawal of common facility services from the defaulting Allotee for the period of the default; this is without prejudice to any other action that the vendor may take to against the Allotee.</li>

            <li>Each Allotee shall pay the ground rent, tenement rates, taxes, assessments, impositions, duties, levies and other outgoings of an annual and recurrent nature which are now and may be charged, levied, assessed or imposed upon the premises by the Federal Capital Territory or the local government authorities during the term to be created or any such terms as contained in its final letter of allocation, Deed of Sublease agreementCertificate of Occupancy and any increment in respect of any such charges. </li>

            <li>The Allotee shall pay Value Added Tax (VAT) being <t t-set="taxs" t-value="5"/><span t-esc="taxs"/>% of the purchase price, &#8358;<span t-esc="'{0:,}'.format(int(taxs*o.payment_invoice.amount_total /100))"/>

               (payable by bank draft to and in the name of the Federal Inland Revenue Service through the Vendor) of the property which tax shall be net of the purchase price as well as other fees (legal fee, service charge and infrastructure leasing charge) to be made under this agreement. </li>

            <li>The property is offered in the condition and state it is and on taking possession the Allotee must expressly accept that the vendor is under no obligation to you except for such fittings and fixtures that the company has specifically covenanted to provide in the property and in particular the vendor shall not be responsible for the provision of kitchenette, , wardrobes, water heaters, air-conditioning units, burglary proofs, external water storage tanks, water metres, water pumps, electrical metres, Picket fence, car port in any of the housing units; the Vendor shall also not lay interlocking blocks or tiles or cement work at the backyard of the housing unit. </li>

            <li>The property shall be used for residential purposes only.</li>

            <li>The keeping of pets and or domestic animals is expressly prohibited.</li>

            <li>Satellite dishes and external communication equipment and devices shall be erected at designated areas as directed by the Vendor.</li>

            <li>That no alteration, modification, addition will be made on the allotted unit without the approval of the Vendor.</li>

            <li>The Allotee shall utilise the services of the Vendor’s electricians and plumbers resident in the Estate in the course of repair or replacement of plumbing or electrical appliances in their respective allotted units to prevent damage of the common electrical and plumbing devices.</li>

            <li>The Allotee shall be at liberty to install alternative power generating devices in its allotted unit such as solar panels, inverters (whether electrical or manual) provided that the Allotee shall not install a generator in any housing unit whether electrical or mechanical</li>

            <li>The Vendor has provided generators within the Estate for the supply of electricity to the Allotee(s) where there is no supply of electricity by the Abuja Electrical Distribution Company (AEDC).</li>

            <li>Payment for electricity supply within the estate by means of generators or other alternative sources provided by the Vendor shall be by prepaid token purchased by each Allotee from the office of the estate facility manager. </li>

            <li>The prepaid token purchased from the office of the Estate Facility Management office caters only for electricity supplied by the Vendor by the installed generators or alternative generating sources. </li>

            <li>The Vendor has provided within the Estate high end transformers, HT and LV panels for the smooth running of electricity services within the Estate. </li>

            <li>All Allotees are to procure from the facility management office an individual check meter for each housing unit. This is compulsory for each housing unit. The individual housing unit check metre is to regulate the energy consumption of each housing unit and upon purchase of the individual housing unit check metre it becomes the property of Allotee and each occupant is responsible for its replacement upon same becoming defective.</li>

            <li>The electricity tariff structure instituted by the Vendor for the Estate for the proper function of the installed generators is based on the aggregation of the Estate energy requirement for the Estate where there is no provision of electricity to the Estate by the Abuja Electrical Distribution Company.</li>

            <li>The Estate electricity tariff which is compulsory for all Allotees also captures the diesel consumption requirements of the Estate and maintenance of the generators provided that and it is hereby agreed by the Allotee that the Estate rate shall be subject to review from time to time by the Vendor.</li>

            <li>The Vendor shall maintain in the Estate a Twenty Four (24) hour Seven days a week uninterrupted electricity supply regime within the Estate by an integration of both electricity supply by the Abuja Electricity Distribution Company with the installed generators on the Estate provided that every Allotee who purchases a housing unit in the Estate also subscribes to the Twenty four (24) hours seven days a week uninterrupted electricity supply regime and hereby covenants not to directly or indirectly subvert the twenty four (24) hour seven days a Week uninterrupted electricity supply regime. </li>

            <li>The Vendor shall continue to reserve the right to revoke the provisional allocation of any Allotee where the activities of any such Allottee(s) are inimical to the Vendor achieving the Twenty four (24) hours seven days a week uninterrupted electricity supply regime within the Estate or where such Allotee engages in any activity of a criminal nature which is punishable under the laws of the Federal Republic of Nigeria.</li>

            <li>The Vendor reserves the right to revoke the provisional allocation of any Allotee where such Allotee instigates the institution of civil or criminal proceedings against the Vendor or its agents or where such Allotee(s) agitates for the civil disturbance within the Estate or disturbs the peace of the office of the Vendor or the Estate Facility Management office.</li>

            <li>The Vendor reserves the right to revoke the provisional allocation of any Allotee where such an Allotee’s action in the opinion of the Vendor amounts to a material breach of the terms of this agreement provided as always and it is hereby agreed by the Vendor and the Allotee that under the circumstances stated in clauses 57, 58 and 59 the Vendor shall issue a revocation notice to any such Allotee whether in occupation of the allotted housing unit or not and thereafter issue the said Allotee or its agent a bank draft in the sum equal to the Allotee’s purchase price( less the 10% charged for administrative fees of the housing unit) any such Allotee shall have one month or such period as granted by the Vendor to move out of the Estate after which period it shall be deemed a trespasser in the Estate and liable to be evicted from the housing unit.</li>

            <li>The provision of portable water in the Estate by the Federal Capital Territory water board shall be complemented by the Vendor providing boreholes within the Estate and the payment for the provision of water to each housing unit shall be by a pre-paid payment system.</li>

            <li>The pre-paid water metres for each housing unit shall be paid for by each Allotee before the date of hand over of each housing unit to each allotee, which payment shall be made to the Vendor.</li>

            <li>The Vendor shall provide prepaid water payment system in each housing unit and Allotee’s shall pay for water supply to their respective housing unit by the purchase of prepaid token from the office of the Estate Facility Management office.</li>

            <li>The prepaid token for the prepaid water metres for each housing unit purchased from the Estate Facility Management office shall cover the cost of water supply by both the water board authority as well as water supplied by the boreholes provided by the Vendor.</li>

            <li>The use of external electricians, plumbers or other artisans is expressly prohibited in the Estate save for carpenters and satellite dish technicians to prevent damage of the central electrical and plumbing devices within the Estate.</li>

            <li>There shall be routine stop and searches conducted on persons going out and coming into the Estate.</li>

            <li>For free flow of vehicular and human traffic within the Estate, double parking, parking on the streets, embankments, pavements and adjourning pavements within the Estate are hereby expressly prohibited. </li>

            <li>The number of domestic and or household staff of each allotted housing unit shall be forwarded by each Allotee to the EstateFacility Management office for the purpose of easy identification of persons residing on the Estate.</li>

            <li>Domestic staff of each housing unit shall be issued with identification cards by the Vendor or Allotee (as the parties may further agree) for easy identification while each Allotee is enjoined to notify the Estate Facility Management office of the termination of the employment of any domestic staff and retrieve such identification cards issued to any such of its staff.</li>

            <li>The Allotee bears a vicarious liability for any act of misdemeanour of any person(s) residing in its unit particularly where the preceding clause 70 is not complied with within a reasonable time. </li>

            <li>That in accordance with the statutorily approved building plans no Allotee shall erect any fence on its allotted unit. </li>

            <li>The dredging or drilling of boreholes on allotted units is prohibited. </li>

            <li>The erection of security house on each allotted unit is prohibited.</li>

            <li>The Allotee hereby covenants that it shall make all payments as stated in this provisional letter of allocation as and when due under this offer.</li>

            <li>The Allotee shall not defer the commencement date for computation of Service charges and Infrastructure leasing charges in respect of their allotted housing unit whether or not the allotted housing unit is occupied and whether or not the Allotee or itstenantsintends to reside in the allotted unit or not.</li>

            <li>No Allotee shall refuse to pay to the Vendor or the Estate Facility Management office the legal fee, service charge and infrastructure leasing charge and other charges listed in this agreementdue in respect of their allotted housing unit where such allotted housing unit is ready for hand over to the allotee on the ground that such allotee does not desire to reside in the said allotted unit or desires to put up same for sale, lease or let to third parties.</li>

            <li>The Vendor hereby warranties that the housing units constructed shall be fit for habitation by the Allotees.</li>

            <li>The Vendor and the Allotee agree that Estate Facility Management office shall manage the Estate as representatives of the Vendor </li>

            <li>Upon the completion of the semi-finished housing unit the Allotee shall be written( by delivered letters or e-mail) or communicated with by telephone by the Estate Facility Management office informing the Allotee of the completion of the semi-finished housing unit and a date agreed to by both the Estate Facility Management office and the Allotee for the inspection of the semi-finished housing unit by the Allottee and the Estate Facility Management office and on the agreed date the Allotee shall carry out the said inspection with the Estate Facility Management office and upon the completion of the inspection the Estate Facility Management office shall check in the Allotee and handed over possession of the semi-finished housing unit to the Allottee. </li>

            <li>The Estate Facility Management personnel and the Allotee shall jointly sign off on the Check- in Form(s) before handing over of the semi-finished housing unit to the Allotee.</li>

            <li>No Allotee shall be allowed entry into, gain access to or enter into physical possession of any semi-finished housing unit in the Estate without going through the inspection, Checking -in and handing over process with the Estate Facility Management Office and where any Allotee has contravened this clause such Allotee shall be deemed to be in material breach of the terms of this agreement and will be ejected by the Estate Facility Management office from the housing unit until such a date as decided by the Estate Facility Management office and communicated to the said Allotee and the Inspection, Checking- in and handover is carried out as between the Estate Facility Management office and the Allotee.</li>

            <li>The Allotee shall assume legal liability for running and maintaining its allotted housing unit once the housing unit has been handed over to the Allotee by the Facility Management office.</li>

            <li>The Inspection, Check- in and Hand Over of the semi-finished housing unit shall be as between the Facility Management office and the Allotee only. </li>

            <li>Where the Vendor has written the Allotee of any housing unit informing such Allotee of the completion of the housing unit and requesting to hand over to the Allotee the said allotted housing unit and has requested the payment of the service charge, infrastructure leasing charge and legal fee in respect of such housing unit and the Allotee refuses, neglects or fails to pay for the said service charges, infrastructural leasing charges and legal fees and these monies remain unremitted and unpaid for a period of Three(3) months after the said letter, the Vendor reserves the right to rescind the sale to the Allotee and revoke the allocation.</li>

            <li>Where any housing unit is revoked by the Vendor subject to the preceding clause 85 of this agreement the Vendor shall refund the deposit paid by the former Allotee of any such housing unit less Ten percent (10%) of the full purchase price deducted by the Vendor as administrative fees when a buyer has been found by the Vendor and the said buyer has made full payment for the housing unit.</li>

            <li>Where any of the Allotee’s stage payment(s)has become due under clauses 1, 2, 3 and 4 of this provisional offer and the Allotee has refused, neglected or failed to make the said stage payment the Vendor shall at its sole discretion amend the terms and conditions of the provisional letter of allocation to extend the completion date by aminimum extension period of six months or such further period as may be communicated by the Vendor to the Allotee and may also increase the purchase price of the housing unit (to a price to be solely determined by the Vendor) The Allotee hereby covenants by the terms of this agreement to accept the extension of completion date of its housing unit whether it receives a notice to that effect or not from the Vendor as agreed by the terms of this agreement.</li>

            <li>Where an Allotee’s stage payment become under clauses 1, 2, 3 and 4 of this provisional offer notwithstanding that the said stage payments have become due before the commencement date for the construction of the semi-finished housing unit of the Allotee as stated in this provisional letter of allocation and the Allotee has consistently and continuously defaulted in making the stage payments as and when due the Vendor shall in its sole discretion relocate the Allotee from that phase of housing unit development within the Estate to the next phase of housing unit development been carried on by the Vendor. The Allotee hereby covenants by the terms of this agreement to accept its relocation to the next phase of housing unit development within the Estate by the Vendor whether it receives a notice to that effect or not from the Vendor.</li>

            <li>All allocations of housing units and housing unit numbers within the Estate are provisional until all payments as contained in the provisional letter of allocation and Final letter of allocation are made by the allotee.</li>

            <li>All allocations of semi-finished housing unit(s) within the Estate are provisional and until all semi-finished housing units are completed, inspected, the Allotee Checked- in and handed over the semi-finished housing unit by the Estate Facility Management office; the Vendor reserves the right at all times to reallocate any housing unit where any such housing unit is yet to be completed, inspected, and handed over by the Estate Facility Management office personnel to any Allotee provided that and it is hereby covenanted by the Vendor that in any such circumstance provision will be made for any allottee affected by any such reallocation by the Vendor such Allotee being allocated a housing unit of the same type in form and specification. </li>

            <li>Both the Vendor and Allotee agree that no right of action against the Vendor exists or is maintainable by any Allotee against the Vendor for any reallocation of housing units by the Vendor in the Estate as no Allotee has proprietary or ownership rights over any housing unit until the Estate Facility Management office notifies the Allotee in writing and a date agreed as between the Facility Management Office and the Allottee for a joint inspection of the housing unit, Checking- in of the Allotee and hand over of the housing unit to the Allotee by the Estate Facility Management office. </li>

            <li>The Allotee shall obtain all information relating to sales, Vendor construction sites, general information, allocations, updates on construction matters and vendor’s products from the vendor’s customers service department.</li>

            <li>No Allotee shall transfer, donate by way of a Power of Attorney, Deed of Sublease, Certificate of Occupancy, sell, assign, convey or otherwise deal with any semi-finished housing unit allotted to it until any such Allotee has completed payment of all fees due (which fees include the payment of the cost price, service charges, infrastructure leasing charges and legal fees) in respect of the said housing unit.</li>

            <li>No Allottee has or shall exercise right of title over any semi-finished housing unit or proprietary rights over any housing unit provisionally allotted to it until all payments as contained in their provisional letter of offer and final letter of offer have been made to the Estate Facility Management office as may be required..</li>

            <li>Where any Allotee who having failed to complete payment for any semi-finished housing unit allotted to them and without notice and approval of the Vendor purports to transfer, sell, assign, convey or otherwise deal with any such housing unit with any third party, such an Allotee shall have their provisional offer revoked immediately by the Vendor and shall be refunded their deposit less Ten (10%)of the full purchase price of any such housing unit which shall be deducted as administrative fees.</li>

            <li>An Allotee who having satisfied all the terms and conditions of sale including the payment to the Vendor of the full purchase price, service charges, infrastructure charges and legal fees and all the fees as stated in this agreement, shall where desirous of effecting a transfer, conveyance, sale, assignment of any such housing unit to a third party, inform the vendor in writing upon which the vendor shall prepare an offer letter, final allocation letter and a Deed of Sublease Agreement in the name of the new allotee. </li>

            <li>Further to the preceding clause 96 of this agreement, the subsisting agreement shall be the Deed of Sublease as between the Vendor and the new Allotee.</li>

            <li>Further to clause 96 of this agreement, the preceding sale agreement and Deed of Sublease as between the Vendor and the preceding Allotee shall be voided and kept in the custody of the Vendor.</li>

            <li>Further to the foregoing clauses both the preceding Allotee and the new Allotee of the housing unit to be assigned, conveyed, transferred or sold shall provide documentary evidence to the Vendor evidencing the transaction between them; which evidence shall include Deed of Sale and evidence of payment for the housing unit. The Vendor shall keep a copy of the aforementioned documents.</li>

            <li>The preceding Allotee shall take out an indemnity agreement in favour of the Vendor in the amount contained in the new sale agreement with the new Allotee. </li>

            <li>The new sale agreement as between the Vendor and the new Allotee shall be subject to a one percent (1%) resale fee charge payable in the name of <b>Brains &amp; Hammers Limited</b>which payment must be in bank draft.</li>

            <li>The Vendor shall not be liable to the Allotee for any delay in completing, commissioning and delivering the allotted housing units on the agreed date of completion if such delay is due to Force Majeure.For the purposes of this offer “<b><i>FORCE MAJEURE</i></b>” shall mean any act, event, or condition beyond reasonable control and without the fault or negligence of the Vendor and or its agents including; acts of God, war, sabotage, riot, insurrection, civil commotion, political impasse, national emergency, weather cyclone, earthquake, landslide and explosion or such like acts).</li>

            <li>The Performance of the terms of this offer shall be suspended for the duration of the disability resulting from the Force Majeure and neither the Vendor nor the Allotee shall be liable for delay or failure in the performance of any of the terms and conditions of this offer for such duration, provided that the Vendor shall promptly give notice of the occurrence of such Force Majeure to the Allotee and agree with the Allotee as to the time, which the Vendor shall, after the cessation of the Force Majeure, discharge its obligations under this agreement.</li>

            <li>The Vendor warranties that all materials to be used for the construction of the semi-finished housing units shall be of good quality and all the personnel to be engaged for the execution of the works shall be sufficiently skilled and competent and further warrants that the roofing and structures shall be without defects, which may be due to the quality of materials used or the competence of the workers engaged, for a period of six (6) months after completion of the housing unit.</li>

            <li>Where the Vendor is unable to complete and deliver the semi-finished housing unit by the completion date it shall give notice to the Allotee and shall give the Allotee a specific time within which it shall complete and handover the housing unit to the Allotee.</li>

            <li>The completion date refers to the date for the completion of the construction of the semi-finished housing unit of the Allotee and does not include the completion of construction works on the commercial areas, green areas and other facilities within the Estate. </li>

            <li>No Allotee who has been handed over their housing unit and is a resident in the Estate shall hold the Vendor liable for any continuing or on -going development or construction work in the Estate or the noise level any such on -going development construction work thin the Estate.</li>

            <li>Further to provisions of this offer the Vendor reserves the right to revoke any allotted unit:-

              <ul class="abc">
                <li>Where the payment terms are not strictly adhered to</li>

                <li>Wheres the Allotee consistently refuses to make stage payments as and when due.</li>

                <li>Where the Allotee refuses, neglects or fails to make stage payments as at when due despite repeated demands via letters or telephone, fax or email correspondence.</li>

                <li>Where the failure of any Allotee to make timely payment is in conflict with the collective interest of other Allotees and is inimical to the timely completion of the housing units.</li>
              </ul>

            </li>

            <li>The Provisional letter of allocation, the Final letter of allocation and the Deed of sublease agreement to be executed by the Vendor and the Allotee with regard to any housing unit purchased in the Estate shall be read and interpreted as one indivisible continuing agreement as between the Allotee and the Vendor and none of the aforementioned agreements shall be interpreted as independent of the other particularly with regard to the clauses dealing with the issue of ownership of infrastructural facilities in the Estatewhich title is vested in the Vendor at all times.</li>

            <li>Where any material clause relating to the aforementioned proprietary rights of the Vendor over all infrastructural facilities in the Estate is inadvertently omitted in the Deed of Sublease but contained in the Provisional letter of allocation and or in the Final letter of allocation such clause(s) shall be deemed to and have the same legal effect of forming part of the clauses of the Deed of Sublease as if same were specifically stated in the Deed of Sublease agreement executed by the Vendor and the Allotee.</li>

            <li>Where any clause is contained in the Provisional letter of allocation, Final letter of allocation or the Deed of Sublease which purports to confer any proprietary right over any of the infrastructural facilities in the Estate on the Allotee(s) both the Vendor and the Allotee hereby agree that any such clause shall be void. </li>

            <li>The Allotee’s proprietary rights within the Estate shall be limited to the housing unit bought by each respective Allotee ONLY and more particularly described by the beacons delineating each housing unit as contained in the schedule to the Deed of sublease agreement to be executed by the vendor with each Allotee. </li>

            <li>The Vendor has ownership of and proprietary rights over all assets and infrastructure within the Estate(save for the housing units sold to the Allotees) which assets and infrastructure include but are not limited to the generators, transformers, ring main units, boreholes, water pumping machines (both surface and submersible),reservoir tanks, feeder pillars, low and high voltage panels, electric fence, street lights, fire hydrants, the security house, the club house, swimming pool, the facility management office, water treatment plants, diesel storage tanks, synchronizing panels, the closed circuit security systems (CCTV) within the Estate as well as the commercial areas and green areas which right has not been derogated by the sale of semi-finished housing units to Allotees within the Estate</li>

            <li>The Vendor shall manage the Estate exclusively utilising its aforementioned assets and infrastructure for the use of all Allotees within the Estate provided that and it is hereby agreed by the Vendor and the Allotee(s) that the application of the infrastructural facilities and assets for the common use of all (Vendor and Allotees by the Estate Facility Management office of the Vendor) within the Estate (hereinafter called the exclusive management agreement) shall not be interpreted as common ownership of the assets and infrastructure in the Estate.</li>

            <li>The exclusive management of the Estate by the Vendor by the Estate Facility Management office is a continuing binding agreement as between the Vendor and the Allotees as well as Allotees’ successors- in title, personal representatives and assigns, which agreement each Allotee hereby covenants by this agreement shall continue in force and automatically renew for successive terms of twenty five (25) years each.</li>

            <li>It is hereby agreed by both the Vendor and the Allotee(s) that the operation of the exclusive property management agreement of the Estate as between the Vendor and all the Allotee(s) within the Estate does not in any way whatsoever confer on the Allotees any beneficial ownership of any of the assets and infrastructure mentioned in Clause 111 of this agreement.</li>

            <li>It is hereby agreed by both the Vendor and each Allotee that the Vendor’s assets stated in this agreementare not owned jointly with any Allotee either individually or collectively and where Allotees form an association collectively to constitute a body corporate, they shall not individually or collectively lay any legal right or claim of ownership of same under any circumstances whatsoever and any such right shall not be imputed by reason of the payment of service charge and infrastructure leasing charge by each Allotee. </li>

            <li>The terms and conditions of this agreement are binding on all Allotees within the Estate, their successors-in- title, personal representatives or assigns and no Allotee shall have the right under any circumstances whatsoever to elect not to be bound by the terms and conditions contained herein.</li>

            <li>No tenant of any Allotee shall have the right to exercise any of the Allotee’s rights under this agreement and in particular shall not have the right to maintain a cause of action against the Vendor with regard to the management of the Estate as by the terms of this agreement both Vendor and Allotee agree that no contractual obligation or privity exists between the Vendor and an Allotee’s tenant.</li>

            <li>Notwithstanding the foregoing provisions contained in this agreement the Vendor and each Allotee hereby agree that the Vendor shall at all times continue to reserve the right to amend, alter, modify or change any or all clauses in this agreement relating to the post completion, handing over of housing units to Allotee(s), Facility Management of the Estate and all such other related ancillary matters on such terms and conditions as the Vendor shall indicate in the final letter of allocation to be issued to each Allotee and any such modification, alteration or amendment of the terms and conditions of this provisional letter of allocation as indicated in the Final letter of allocation and the Deed of Sublease agreement shall be binding on each Allottee as if any such alterations, amendments or modification were terms and conditions contained in this provisional letter of allocation.</li>

          </ol>
         <br/>
        <p>If the above terms and conditions are acceptable to you, please indicate by signing in the space provided in our acceptance form.</p>
         <p align="justify">
                  Thank you,
				</p>
                <p align="justify">
                  Yours Faithfully
				</p>

       <tr><td style="padding-top:4%;">
             <img src="https://imgur.com/FYvOMgW.jpg" style="max-height: 150px;" />

            </td></tr>
        <p align="justify">
            <strong>AUTHORIZED SIGNATORY</strong>

        </p>
        <tr><td style="padding-top:2%;">
                            For: Brains &amp; Hammers Limited
		</td></tr>

        <p align="justify">
            <u>ACCEPTED BY OFFEREE</u>
            <u></u>
        </p>
        <p align="justify">
            NAME:………………………………………………………………........
        </p>
        <p align="justify">
            SIGNATURE………………………………………………………………....
        </p>
        <p align="justify">
            DATE:……………………………………………………………………….....
        </p>
        <p align="justify">
            TELEPHONE NUMBER…………………………………………………..
        </p>
				<br />
        <p align="justify">
            <u></u>
        </p>
        <p align="justify">
            <u>WITNESSED BY:</u>
            <u></u>
        </p>
        <p align="justify">
            NAME:………………………………………………………………………....
        </p>
        <p align="justify">
            ADDRESS:…………………………………………………………………...
        </p>
        <p align="justify">
            SIGNATURE:………………………………………………………………….
        </p>
        <p align="justify">
            TELEPHONE NUMBER………………………………………………….
        </p>

      </div>
      </t>
    </template>
    <!--<template id="galadimawa_carcas_offer_letter_report">
		<t t-call="report.offer_letter">
			<t t-foreach="doc_ids" t-as="doc_id">
				<t t-raw="translate_doc(doc_id,doc_model,'building','construction_rewrite.galadimawa_carcas_offer_letter_report_document')"/>
			</t>
		</t>
		</template>-->

  </data>
</odoo>
